<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Early Stage on Byran Dai - Developer Blog</title>
    <link>/./categories/early-stage/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Early Stage on Byran Dai - Developer Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/./categories/early-stage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Refocusing on updates</title>
      <link>/./2018/02/refocusing-on-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/./2018/02/refocusing-on-updates/</guid>
      <description>I’m getting back into writing again, and this time sticking with it. Daily updates, short blurbs, long-form pieces on particularly pensive days, you name it.
Our team continues to grow as more data specialists are sent over from our community agencies and ACCES-VR partnerships. It’s been a wonderful experience working with these men and women, and in particular it’s an opportunity to create a new corporate model for working with this population that provides professional development opportunities and strong productivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selling the idea</title>
      <link>/./2018/01/selling-the-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/./2018/01/selling-the-idea/</guid>
      <description>Quick update on my end, only because so much of the work I’ve been doing has been going out and talking, listening, meeting, emailing.
If there was one skill that I’ve developed over this past month, it’s been how to make a cleaner and more succinct pitch about Daivergent to anyone who will listen. I buy strongly into the six second elevator pitch from a blog post I read from Rajesh Anandan, one of the trailblazing industry leaders in this space.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>