<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Byran Dai - Developer Blog</title>
    <link>/./post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Byran Dai - Developer Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/./post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Refocusing on updates</title>
      <link>/./2018/02/refocusing-on-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/./2018/02/refocusing-on-updates/</guid>
      <description>I’m getting back into writing again, and this time sticking with it. Daily updates, short blurbs, long-form pieces on particularly pensive days, you name it.
Our team continues to grow as more data specialists are sent over from our community agencies and ACCES-VR partnerships. It’s been a wonderful experience working with these men and women, and in particular it’s an opportunity to create a new corporate model for working with this population that provides professional development opportunities and strong productivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selling the idea</title>
      <link>/./2018/01/selling-the-idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/./2018/01/selling-the-idea/</guid>
      <description>Quick update on my end, only because so much of the work I’ve been doing has been going out and talking, listening, meeting, emailing.
If there was one skill that I’ve developed over this past month, it’s been how to make a cleaner and more succinct pitch about Daivergent to anyone who will listen. I buy strongly into the six second elevator pitch from a blog post I read from Rajesh Anandan, one of the trailblazing industry leaders in this space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The critical minutiae (or the administrative slog of setting up a new company), Part 1</title>
      <link>/./2018/01/the-critical-minutiae-or-the-administrative-slog-of-setting-up-a-new-company-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/./2018/01/the-critical-minutiae-or-the-administrative-slog-of-setting-up-a-new-company-part-1/</guid>
      <description>This is the part of the story that doesn’t get shared often. You don’t usually hear the courageous startup founder extol about how they successfully secured low rates on state unemployment insurance. There aren’t a lot of feel-good stories about successfully filing Form 2553 with the IRS electing your new company as an S-Corp.
This is intended to be a short and sweet post of what I’ve had to do so far to set up this company, roughly in chronological order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting Daivergent Inc</title>
      <link>/./2017/12/starting-daivergent-inc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/./2017/12/starting-daivergent-inc/</guid>
      <description>One week ago, I submitted paperwork to incorporate a company called Daivergent. If you remember from the first post of my blog, I was deciding between two projects.
develop this new data collection service to yadda yadda yadda…
build the next generation of group homes for adults with intellectual and developmental disabilities (IDD), addressing the signficant caregiver stress, growing prevalence of children with IDD transitioning into adulthood, and untapped potential of these adults to be contributing members of their communities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Decision Genie Alexa Skill (Mini-Project) - Introduction and Setup</title>
      <link>/./2017/11/the-decision-genie-alexa-skill-mini-project---introduction-and-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/./2017/11/the-decision-genie-alexa-skill-mini-project---introduction-and-setup/</guid>
      <description>A Convenient MotivationI was introduced to Amazon Web Services (AWS) during my time at Quartet, and I found myself wanting to learn how to make the most out of the platform. At the same time, I had received four Amazon Echo Dots as a result of a promotional code mistake by Amazon that resulted in the Dot being sold for free.
What better way to leverage the two than a good old-fashioned Alexa Skill?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So What&#39;s Next?</title>
      <link>/./2017/11/so-whats-next/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/./2017/11/so-whats-next/</guid>
      <description>“So what are you doing next?”
Like clockwork, this was the question I got asked when I’d tell someone I quit my job. A week and a half later, I’m still figuring out the right answer, the right way to phrase “I just want some protected time to build an idea.”
I left my Data Science position at Quartet Health the weekend before Thanksgiving. I felt the time was right to dive headfirst into a few projects that I had been bouncing around for a while, while also focusing heavily on strengthening my technical and programming skillsets.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>